Finding Aid for Center for the Education of Women (University of Michigan) Records, 1919-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Central Office Files 1961-1998
  - Topical Files
    Highlights of the series include records on several major CEW initiatives, including the Evening Program, the Women in Science Program, the center's Scholarship Awards, various programs for international women, its research activities, its many conferences and workshops, and its involvement in university-wide efforts to document and improve the climate for women and minority students, faculty and staff. Also included in the series are a large quantity of public relations material and a small body of photographs that were filed as a group. The locations of other photographs, that have been left with their related topical documents, are indicated by the note '(includes photo)' in the folder listing.
    The researcher should note that (in addition to the overlaps between the Topical Files and other series, mentioned in the collection-wide scope and content note) there are a number of overlapping subjects within the Topical series:
    'Black Women In Transition' and 'Perspectives on Black Women'
    'Centennial 1970' and 'Women on Campus'
    'Employment', 'Job', and 'Michigan Civil Service Commission'
    Additionally, there are two related clusters of files dealing with statistics and quantitative data on the climate for women and minorities at the University of Michigan in general and on CEW participants in particular:
    [The climate for women and minorities]: 'Affirmative Action', 'Central Coordinating Committee for Women and Minority Services', 'Statistics on UM Enrollment of Women', and files starting with 'Women and Minority...'
    [CEW participants and other non-traditional students]: CEW research program, 'Grants-Ford Foundation', 'Non-traditional/Older Students Study', 'Participant Data', 'Report on UM Women', and 'Research Program'
    Finally, researchers looking for records of CEW's programs and events should look under individual program names, in the 'Programs by Academic Year' files, and in the 'Publicity' files.
    - 1962-1998
      - Abortion 1986 (Box 7)
      - Academic Women's Caucus 1983-1993 (Box 7)
      - Administrative Intern Program 1991 (Box 7)
      - Admissions 1967-1973 (Box 7)
      - Adult Education Association 1967-1968 (Box 7)
      - Advocacy 1974, 1983 (Box 7)
      - Affirmative Action 1971-1972, 1981-1983, 1989-1991 (Box 7)
      - Age Concerns Task Force of the ACAAP (Advisory Committee on the Affirmative Action Programs) 1981-1982 (Box 7)
      - Aging and Ageism 1972-1976 (Box 7)
      - Alumnae Council 1971-1973 (Box 7)
      - American Association of University Women 1970-1973, 1978 (Box 7)
      - American Council on Education 1972, 1981 (Box 7)
      - ADA (Americans with Disabilities Act) Self Evaluation 1992 (Box 7)
      - Anniversaries
        - Twenty Fifth
          - Conference Program 1989-1990 (Box 7)
          - Correspondence 1990 (Box 7)
          - Kick-Off Luncheon 1989-1990 (Box 7)
          - Leadership Panel 1990 (Box 7)
          - Publicity 1990 (Box 7)
          - Marguerite Ross Barnett 1989-1991 (Box 7)
          - Betty Dooley 1990 (Box 7)
          - Arvonne Fraser 1990 (Box 7)
          - Paula Giddings 1990 (Box 7)
            (includes photo)
          - Alice-Kessler Harris 1990 (Box 7)
          - Nellie M. Varner 1990 (Box 7)
        - Thirtieth 1994 (Box 7)
      - Arrow Program for Undergraduate Women
        - Correspondence 1972-1974 (Box 7)
        - Evaluations 1972-1975 (Box 7)
        - Miscellaneous 1971-1974 (Box 7)
        - Orientation Programs 1972-1975 (Box 7)
        - Publicity 1972-1974 (Box 7)
        - Residence Halls 1972-1974 (Box 7)
        - Staff Memos 1972-1974 (Box 7)
        - Trigger Tapes 1972-1974 (Box 7)
      - Assertiveness Training for the Black Woman (Workshops) 1977-1978 (Box 7)
      - Daphne Bennett Visits 1986-1987 (Box 7)
      - Black Women In Transition
        - Background and Precursors 1976-1977 (Box 7)
        - Conference and Follow Ups 1978 (Box 7)
        - Ongoing Programs 1980-1989 (Box 7)
      - Black Women's Educational Policy and Research Network Midwestern Regional Conference 1981 (Box 7)
        (CEW co-sponsored)
      - Brown Bags and Tray Lunches 1975-1980 (Box 7)
        (also see Conversations at the Center)
      - Capital Campaign 1981-1983 (Box 7)
      - Catalyst 1969-1973 (Box 7)
      - Centennial 1970 1969- (Box 7)
      - Centennial 1970--Honorary Degrees 1969-1970 (Box 7)
        (Mina Rees and Esther Peterson, includes photo)
      - Central Coordinating Committee for Women and Minority Services 1978 (Box 7)
        (Also see 'Women and Minority Services Staff')
      - Child Care Projects 1969-1976, 1981-1982 (Box 7)
      - College Level Exam Program 1968-1974 (Box 7)
      - Commission for Women
        - Affirmative Action Reorganization Activities 1979-1980 (Box 7)
        - Cluster Coordinating Committee 1970-1973, 1979 (Box 7)
        - Coalition Event 1991 (Box 7)
        - Future Goals 1971 (Box 7)
        - History (1971-1977) May 22, 1978 (Box 7)
        - Membership Committee 1982, 1989 (Box 7)
        - Minutes 1977, 1980-1988 (Box 8)
        - Miscellaneous 1978-1980, 1988-1990 (Box 8)
        - Reports/Surveys 1971-1978, 1981, 1991 (Box 8)
        - Taking Charge of Your Future (Workshop, October 30, 1986) 1986-1987 (Box 8)
        - WIN [Women's Information Network] Bulletin, 1972-1977 (Box 8)
        - Women's Network 1980-1984 (Box 8)
      - Committee for Gender Research 1980, undated (Box 8)
      - Committee to Study the Status of Women in Graduate Education 1972-1973 (Box 8)
      - Community Focus (CEW articles for North Campus Family Housing newsletter), ca 1980, 1986-1987, 1990, 1993 (Box 8)
      - Community Organizations and Resources 1969-1979 (Box 8)
      - Compensation Program Task Force 1988-1989 (Box 8)
      - Computer Committee 1983-1984 (Box 8)
      - Computer Task Force 1986 (Box 8)
      - Conferences (Binder), circa 1965-1983 (Box 8)
      - Connections (Program for returning, non-traditional students), circa 1990-1994 (Box 8)
      - Conversations at the Center 1968-1974 (Box 8)
        (also see "Brown Bags and Tray Lunches")
      - Counseling 1973-1979, 4 folders (Box 8)
      - Counseling Staff Notes (Binder), circa 1971-1974 (Box 8)
      - Coursepack for Peer Counselors 1994 (Box 8)
      - Critical Difference Grants 1975, 1978-1986, 1992-1993 (Box 8)
      - Danforth Foundation Fellowships 1964-1966 (Box 8)
      - Dependent Care/Family Care Task Force 1984-1989 (Box 8)
      - Directorship Search 1984-1985 (Box 8)
      - Donor List 1990 (Box 8)
      - Employment Opportunities (UM) 1966-1973, 1979 (Box 8)
      - Employment Questionnaire 1968-1969 (Box 8)
      - Employment Trends and Opportunities--Part-Time 1966-1972, 1977 (Box 8)
      - Evening Program,: May 1969-1974/75, 6 folders (Box 8)
        (also see Pat Wulp files for Evening Program records after 1981, 1969/70 folder includes application form for Anne Duderstadt)
      - Evening Program 1975/76-1981/82, 7 folders (Box 9)
      - Evening Program Reports and Surveys 1970-1985 (Box 9)
      - Financial Assistance--"Memo to a Friend" 1968-1969 (Box 9)
        (Fundraising campaign prior to/in conjunction with the 1970 Centennial of Women)
      - Funding Requests and Cooperative Programs 1988-1995, 5 folders (Box 9)
      - "The Future for Women at the University of Michigan" (Public forum, April 13, 1988) 1988 (Box 9)
      - Grants
        - Best Products Foundation 1985-1990 (Box 9)
        - Ford Foundation
          - General 1973-1983 (Box 9)
          - Questionnaires 1977, 1981 (Box 9)
          - Research 1972-1984 (Box 9)
          - Seed Grants 1977-1980 (Box 9)
        - Funded Programs 1988-1994 (Box 9)
        - Henry Luce Foundation/Clare Booth Luce Fund 1991, 1998 (Box 9)
        - Mary Malcomson Raphael Fund 1980-1992 (Box 9)
        - Michigan Women's Foundation 1987-1989 (Box 9)
        - Proposals 1976-1983, 1991 (Box 9)
      - Groups 1973-1980 (Box 9)
        (Also see Program files and the names of specific group workshops and classes)
      - Matina Horner Honorary Degree Nomination 1988-1989 (Box 9)
      - Institute for Administrative Advancement of Academic Women 1973 (Box 9)
      - International Women's Programs
        - General/Miscellaneous
          - Funding and Grants 1985-1988, 2 folders (Box 9)
          - Job Hunt Club (specifically for foreign women), Winter 1988 (Box 9)
          - Professional Opportunities for International Women (Panel, 11/4/1988), Fall 1988 (Box 9)
          - Publicity 1987-1988 (Box 9)
        - Paving the Way (Program for foreign women graduate students)
          - General 1985-1986 (Box 9)
          - NAFSA (National Association for Foreign Student Affairs) Grant--Background, ca 1982-1985, undated (Box 9)
          - Proposal 1984 (Box 10)
          - Readings and Background Material undated (Box 10)
          - Readings for Fall 1986 (Box 10)
          - Readings for Session VIII on Re-Entry (undated) (Box 10)
          - Report 1985-1986 (Box 10)
        - Professional Development Program for International Women
          (At first titled 'Professional Development Program for Wives of Foreign Students')
          - Advisory Committee 1983-1986 (Box 10)
          - Applicant Lists 1984-1987 (Box 10)
          - Budget 1985-1988 (Box 10)
          - Correspondence with Donors 1982-1984 (Box 10)
          - Funding Proposals 1983-1987 (Box 10)
          - Guidelines for Internship Sponsors, ca 1980s (Box 10)
          - Intern Certification Letters 1984-1987 (Box 10)
          - Internship--Blank Forms and Form Letters 1983-1986 (Box 10)
          - Miscellaneous, ca 1980s (Box 10)
          - Participant Lists 1984-1987 (Box 10)
          - Professional Communication Skills Workshops (Evaluations) 1985-1988 (Box 10)
          - Program Planning 1983-1987 (Box 10)
          - Publicity (General) 1983-1986 (Box 10)
          - Publicity (Forms and Flyers) 1983-1987, undated (Box 10)
          - Report 1984 (Box 10)
        - Undergraduate Initiatives
          (Professional Development and Academic Support for International Undergraduates at the University of Michigan)
          - Accounts 1987-1988 (Box 10)
          - Paper Presentation 1987 (Box 10)
          - Program Planning and Evaluation 1987-1988 (Box 10)
          - Proposals 1987-1988 (Box 10)
          - Workshop Handouts, Winter 1988, 2 folders (Box 10)
          - Workshop Speakers, Winter 1988 (Box 10)
        - WIGS
          (acronym unknown; proposed program for international graduate student women)
          - Program Planning for Fall 1986, 1985-1986 (Box 10)
          - Re-Entry Interest Forms 1987 (Box 10)
          - Re-Entry Readings, Winter 1987 (Box 10)
        - Applicants Not Accepted 1984-1986, 2 folders (Box 42)
          [SR RESTRICTED until January 1 2061 ]
        - Fall 1986 Interns, 1986-1987 (Box 42)
          [SR RESTRICTED until January 1 2062 ]
        - Intern Files
          - Alphabetical 1984-1986, 16 folders (Box 42)
          - Fall 1986, 1984-1987, 4 folders (Box 42)
        - Interview Summaries 1984 (Box 42)
          [SR RESTRICTED until January 1 2059 ]
        - Possible Interns for Spring 1985 ca 1984-1985 (Box 42)
          [SR RESTRICTED until January 1 2060 ]
        - Summer/Fall 1984 Applications, ca 1984-1986 (Box 42)
      - Jean W. Campbell Women's Leadership Fund
        - Correspondence 1988 (Box 10)
        - Guest and Donor Lists 1988 (Box 10)
        - Notes 1988 (Box 10)
        - Photographs 1988 (Box 10)
      - Job Opportunity Interviews--Local Research Organizations 1965 (Box 10)
      - Job Opportunities for Medical Wives 1965 (Box 10)
      - Job Survey--Ann Arbor Firms 1966 (Box 10)
        ('Opportunities for Mature Women')
      - Job Survey--University of Michigan 1965-1966 (Box 10)
      - Legislation 1973-1978 (Box 10)
      - Library
        - Acquisitions lists 1977, 1990-1996, 3 folders (Box 10)
          (See 'Library News/Notes' for Library Acquisitions lists dating from 1980-1990)
        - Acquisitions policy, ca 1984-1989 (Box 10)
        - Annual Reports and Statistics 1976-1985 (Box 10)
        - Bibliographies (CEW) 1969-1996, 2 folders (Box 10)
        - Bibliographies (UM) 1970-1975 (Box 10)
        - Correspondence 1987-1994, 2 folders (Box 10)
        - "Library News Notes" 1980-1989, 3 folders (Box 11)
          (Previously titled "Library Notes"; includes acquisitions lists)
        - "Library Operations Manual", circa 1987 (Box 11)
        - Miscellaneous 1975-1979, 1986-1989, undated (Box 11)
        - Planning 1985-1986 (Box 11)
        - Procedures and Policies 1977-1978 (Box 11)
        - Resource Lists and Locators 1972-1995 (Box 11)
        - "A Review and Evaluation of the University of Michigan Center for Continuing Education of Women Library" 1989 (Box 11)
        - Staffing Recommendations 1990 (Box 11)
        - User survey 1972-1974 (Box 11)
        - Women's Resource Center Award Application 1980 (Box 11)
      - LSA Commission on Graduation Requirements, ca 1970-1975 (Box 11)
      - Married Student Task Force 1971-1972 (Box 11)
      - Michigan Civil Service Commission Part-Time Work Project
        - Correspondence 1967-1973 (Box 11)
        - Mailing Materials and Response Procedures 1969-1970 (Box 11)
        - Planning and Evaluation 1966-1973 (Box 11)
        - Returned CEW Questionnaires 1970 (Box 11)
          (Includes photograph)
        - Written Inquiries 1970-1972, 1975 (Box 11)
      - Michigan League as Headquarters 1964-1967 (Box 11)
      - Michigan Network of Women's Centers 1986-1988 (Box 11)
      - MSA (Michigan Student Assembly) Women's Symposium 1988 (Box 11)
      - Michigan Women in Science 1972-1973 (Box 11)
      - Michigan Women's Commission 1963-1973, 1985, 2 folders (Box 11)
        (Earlier names include 'Governor's Commission on the Status of Women' and 'Governor's Commission on Women')
      - Michigan Women's Leadership Project 1993 (Box 11)
      - Michigan Women's Political Caucus 1971 (Box 11)
      - Minority Conferences 1977-1980 (Box 11)
        (e.g. 'Minority Women and Families', 3/26/1979 and 'Career Development for Black Women', 12/6/1980)
      - Miscellaneous 1972-1982, 1986-1988, undated (Box 11)
      - NAWDAC (National Association of Women Deans and Counselors) CEW Pre-Conference--'Paving Passages for the Adult Woman: Workable Ideas in Women's Continuing Education' March 28-29, 1978 (Box 11)
      - National Council for Research on Women 1970-1974, 1982-1988, 1992-1993, 3 folders (Box 11)
        (Previous names include: ca 1970 'National Coalition for Research on Women's Education and Employment'; 1970s 'National Coalition for Research on Women's Education and Development')
      - New Careers in Community Service (Conference/Workshop, 3/27/1968) 1968 (Box 11)
      - New Patterns of Employment (Conference/Workshop, 3/29/1966)--Planning 1966 (Box 11)
      - New Patterns of Employment (Conference/Workshop, 3/29/1966)--Speeches 1966 (Box 11)
      - New Research on Women I and II (Conferences 3/15/1973 and 3/19/1975), 1973-1975 (Box 11)
      - Non-Traditional/Older Students Study
        - Planning 1972, 1977-1979 (Box 11)
        - Questionnaires and Report Preparation 1980-1981 (Box 11)
        - Draft Report 1981 (Box 12)
        - Summary Report "Non-Traditional Student Attitudes and Needs: Summary Report of a Survey of Older Students, Winter 1980" 1982 (Box 12)
      - Office Procedures 1991-1992 (Box 12)
      - Office Procedures Manual July 1986 (Box 12)
      - Opportunities for Women through Education (Conference/Workshop, 3/16/1965) 1965 (Box 12)
      - Panel on Alternative Approaches to Graduate Education 1972-1974 (Box 12)
      - "Part-Time Professional/Administrative Employment at the University of Michigan" (Parts 1 and 2, January and August 1973) 1973 (Box 12)
      - Participant Data (Statistics and Reports) 1965-1986, 4 folders (Box 12)
      - Participant News and Notes 1976-1977 (Box 12)
      - Perspectives on Black Women (Conference, 3/20/1976) 1976 (Box 12)
      - Photographs
        - A Dangerous Experiment by Dorothy McGuigan
          (Also see Dorothy McGuigan and Ruth Bordin files)
          - Athletics (Box 12)
          - Children (Box 12)
          - Class Groups and Libraries (Box 12)
          - Individuals (Box 12)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
          - Political and Social Activities (Box 12)
          - Rooms and Dormitories (Box 12)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
        - Newsletter, Fall 1976 (Box 12)
        - A Sampler of Women's Studies (Box 12)
        - A Sampler of Women's Studies, negatives (Box 12)
        - Young Mothers (Box 12)
      - President's Advisory Commission on Women's Issues 1988-1994 (Box 12)
      - Problems of Women's Continuing Education: A Research Symposium 3/1/1977 (Box 12)
      - Professional Women's Internship Program 1994 (Box 12)
      - Program Evaluations (Time-Cost-Effectiveness Assessments) 1975-1982 (Box 12)
      - Programs (Binder), ca 1967-1982 (Box 12)
      - Programs (By Academic Year), 1966-1970/71, undated, 4 folders (Box 12)
        (folder for 1966-1968/69 includes photo)
      - Programs (By Academic Year), 1971/72-December 1982, 9 folders (Box 13)
        (See Pat Wulp files for Program records after 1981 also see under the names of specific programs and events)
      - Psychology 402 (Women in Non-Traditional Occupations), B. Gutek, ca 1975-1977 (Box 13)
      - Publications, ca 1965-1976 (Box 13)
      - Publicity
        - General 1964-1978, 1982-1995, undated, 6 folders (Box 13)
          (files for 1982-1995 also include clippings and press releases)
        - Newspaper Clippings 1963-1973 (Box 13)
          (includes photos)
        - Press Releases (CEW) 1968-1980 (Box 13)
        - Press Releases (UM) 1964-1979 (Box 13)
      - Rackham Administrative Council Meetings 1975-1978 (Box 13)
      - Re-Entry (a.k.a. 'Day on Campus') 1967, 1975-1977 (Box 13)
      - Report on UM Women 1977-1978 (Box 13)
      - Research Program 1976-1986, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - Correspondence from CEW Scholars 1971-1977 (Box 14)
      - Scholarship Awards 1969-1983, 1988-1994, 4 folders (Box 14)
      - Scholarship Awards Binders
        - 1969/70-1975/76 ca January 1970-May 1975 (Box 14)
        - 1976/77-1984/85 ca October 1975-May 1984 (Box 14)
        - 1979/80-1981/82 ca April 1979-May 1981 (Box 14)
        - 1985/86-1986/87 ca October 1984-May 1986 (Box 14)
        - 1978/88-1992/93 ca October 1986-May 1992 (Box 14)
        - Scholarship Awards Readers' Binder for 1989/90-1992/93
          - Part I (Scholarship Readers' Packet) January 1990 (Box 14)
          - Part II (Main Binder), ca 1990-1992 (Box 14)
          - Part III (1990/91 Readers' Materials) 1989-1990 (Box 14)
        - Scholarship Awards Towsley Binder: Historical and 1993/94
          - Part I (Frontmatter), ca 1992-1993 (Box 14)
          - Part II (Main Binder), ca 1975-1993 (Box 14)
          - Part III (Endmatter), ca 1993-1994 (Box 14)
        - Eligibility Correspondence 1980-1985 (Box 42)
      - Sexual Harassment--Historical Legislation and Policies, ca 1979-1980 (Box 15)
      - Sexual Harassment Implementation Team
        - Correspondence 1987-1993 (Box 15)
        - Policies 1991-1993 (Box 15)
        - Training 1992 (Box 15)
      - Singles and Single Heads of Households 1973-1976 (Box 15)
        (Programs and support groups, e.g. 'Single Again', 'Alone Again')
      - Speaker Biographies/Profiles 1973, 1976-1984 (Box 15)
      - Staff Activities: Time Motion Study and Overtime Tracking 1974 (Box 15)
      - Staff Classifications
        - Appeals and Implementation 1972-1977 (Box 15)
        - Clerical Personnel 1967-1978 (Box 15)
        - Descriptions and Time Use Estimates 1981-1992 (Box 15)
        - P/A (Professional and Administrative) Salary Equity Study 1971-1972 (Box 15)
      - Staff Evaluation Materials 1985-1989 (Box 15)
      - Staff Materials (Miscellaneous) 1969-1991 scattered dates (Box 15)
      - Statistics on UM Enrollment of Women 1962-1992, 3 folders (Box 15)
      - Student Records Policies (FOIA, FERPA, and Confidentiality) 1974, 1977-1978, 1985-1986 (Box 15)
      - Summerscience for Girls (Dorothy Lawshe) 1988-1989 (Box 15)
      - Task Force on the Composition of the Student Body 1973-1974 (Box 15)
      - Testimonials 1967-1973, undated (Box 15)
        (also see 'Thank you letters')
      - Traditional Students Task Force 1988 (Box 15)
      - US Department of Labor Women's Bureau 1967-1972 (Box 15)
      - University Health Service Talk 1991 (Box 15)
      - UM Dearborn Women's Center--Proposal for Fellowships for Returning Students 1978 (Box 15)
      - UM Flint Re-Entry Center 1988 (Box 15)
      - UM Flint Women's Center 1991-1992 (Box 15)
      - University Resource Guide and Journal, ca 1965-1971 (Box 15)
      - Videos ('Two Women Twenty Years' and Trigger Tapes) 1971-1977 (Box 15)
        (folder prefaced by a note from around the 1990s)
      - Visitors to the Center (Box 15)
      - Volunteer Resource Bank 1991 (Box 15)
      - Washtenaw County Committee on the Status of Women 1970-1971 (Box 15)
      - Women and Higher Education 1977 (Box 15)
      - Women and Minority Concerns (Statistics on Levels of UM Staffing of Women and Minorities) 1969-1988 (Box 16)
      - Women and Minority Services Staff 1969-1972, 1976-1988 (Box 16)
      - Women and Minority Staffing and Enrollment at UM (Clippings Binder), 1970s (Box 16)
      - Women and the Workplace (Symposium, 3/6/1986) 1986 (Box 16)
      - Women at the University of Michigan (Report to the President), 1992 (Box 16)
      - Women at the University of Michigan, Volume II, 1993 (Box 16)
      - Women at the University of Michigan, Volume III, 1996 (Box 16)
      - Women in a Technological Society (WITS) 1985-1987 (Box 16)
      - Women in Action (Conference, 3/26/1969)
        - Biographies 1969 (Box 16)
        - Conference Notes and Transcripts 1969 (Box 16)
        - Conference Publications and Handouts 1969 (Box 16)
        - Display Materials (Correspondence) 1969 (Box 16)
        - General Planning 1968-1969 (Box 16)
        - Publicity and Press 1969 (Box 16)
      - Women in School and at Work (Series February-April 1967), Planning, 1966-1967 (Box 16)
      - Women in School and at Work (Series February-April 1967), Speeches, 1967 (Box 16)
      - Women in Science
        (WIS, later became WISE--Women in Science and Engineering [WISE]; also see WISE collection)
        - Administrative
          - General 1979-1989, 1992-1994, 3 folders (Box 16)
          - GASAT (Girls and Science and Technology) IV 1987 (Box 16)
          - Miscellaneous Articles and Brochures 1983-1989, undated (Box 16)
        - Correspondence February 1982-April 1983, 5 folders (Box 16)
        - Correspondence May 1983-December 1985, 16 folders (Box 17)
        - Programs
          - Miscellaneous Chronological
            - 1987-1988, 3 folders (Box 17)
            - Winter 1989
              - Graduate Women in Engineering 1/12/1989 (Box 17)
              - Women in Medical School 2/7/1989 (Box 17)
                (panel for undergraduates)
              - Girl Scouts Program 2/11/1989 (Box 17)
              - Women in Science: Graduate School 2/14/1989 (Box 17)
              - Moms in Science 3/8/1989 (Box 17)
              - Lectures March 1989 (Box 17)
                (Regina Marantz-Sanchez, 3/29/1989 and the Warner Lambert Lecture given by Dr. Gloria Johnson Powell, 3/16/1989)
              - Whitmore Lake High School 4/19/1989 (Box 17)
            - 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box 17)
          - Internships